easytithe.com 2014-09-03

# Privacy Policy - Online Giving For The Church - Accept Online Donations with Easy Tithe

Automatic Recurring Donations

Debit Card Only Option

Custom Branded Interface

Mobile Giving

Pledge Tracking/Management

Unlimited Funds/Campaigns

Unlimited Users

PCI DSS Compliant & SSL Secure

Graphical Trends Display

No Term Contract

### Free Bonus:

Unlimited Custom Event Forms!

Free Online Store!

Free Virtual Terminal

**_Document Last Modified_ :  June 5, 2013**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Easy Tithe collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").

**Privacy**  
Users' privacy is very important to Easy Tithe. Easy Tithe is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Easy Tithe. This Web site is not directed at children under 13 years of age.

**The Information We Collect**  
Easy Tithe may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Easy Tithe may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site, the type of computer used, or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**  
Easy Tithe may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Easy Tithe and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with Easy Tithe and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Easy Tithe may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Easy Tithe, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Easy Tithe may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Easy Tithe's business.

**Maintenance of Information**  
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**Questions**  
Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by contacting Easy Tithe. 

Easy tithe has been a great resource and has help drive people to our new website. As a result they are telling there friends about it and our traffic has increased immensely. Just in online giving we have gone from 700.00 the first month to over 5,000.00 in the 3rd month. Thanks Easy Tithe!

Nate H.|Executive Pastor|Medina, OH

EasyTithe has been the simplest, most powerful integration for online giving to our website. Our church is approximately 250-300 people and its been one of the best tools yet. Its far better than anything weve seen or tested before, and now, we couldnt do without it. Highly, highly recommend this program!!

Matt S.|Administrator|Wharton, TX

Easy Tithe offers us all of the benefits of online giving without the hassles of maintaining the service. They take care of the maintenance and security aspects of the interface for us. Job well done!

Christopher G.|IT Systems Engineer|Hilton, NY
